247-host.com 2007-06-29

# 247-host.com Web Hosting Solutions Worldwide

|  | 

| 

****Privacy Statement****  
  
---  
  
**Privacy Statement  
** 247-host.com respects your privacy and works hard to safeguard the privacy of your Internet activity. We created this privacy statement to demonstrate our firm commitment to the privacy of the users of our websites. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy, and how we treat personally identifiable information collected from our visitors and users.  
**Personally Identifiable Information  
** Privacy concerns center on information that can be associated with a particular individual or entity. This information is often referred to as "personally identifiable information" and includes, for example, such things as a customer's name, address, telephone number, or e-mail address.  
**Disclosure  
** 247-host.com will not disclose to outside parties any personally identifiable information obtained from the registration for or use of 247-host.com's services without the consent of the customer (except as required by subpoena or other legal process, cases where 247-host.com suspects fraud, or in the case of imminent physical harm to customers or others). When 247-host.com uses agents, contractors or other companies to perform services on its behalf, 247-host.com will require that they protect your personally identifiable information consistent with this Policy.  
**Collection and Use of Personally Identifiable Information**  
247-host.com collects and uses personally identifiable information obtained from you and from other sources for billing purposes, to provide and change service, to anticipate and resolve problems with your service, or to identify, create and inform you of products, services or special offers that better meet your needs. 247-host.com will not sell or disclose any of your personally identifiable information to other companies or organizations without your consent, unless compelled by a court order or subpoena. We reserve the right, however, to convey any information we collect from or about you to a successor-in-interest or business partner.  
In accordance with the Federal Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA), 247-host.com will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without first requesting verifiable parental consent.  
**Collection of Internet Usage Data  
** 247-host.com's network gathers information about Internet usage such as IP address information of users connecting to your site, IP address information of FTP transfers, number of e-mails sent, and data transfer usage.  
**E-mail  
** 247-host.com will not read your outgoing or incoming e-mail except in cases where 247-host.com suspects a user is violating Terms of Service and Acceptable Use Policies. 247-host.com or its agents may store e-mail messages for a brief period of time and could be compelled to disclose the messages in order to comply with a court order or subpoena, if it is necessary to disclose this information to protect 247-host.com's network or an individual's safety or security.  
**Security  
** 247-host.com has in place security measures and policy guidelines to protect your customer identifiable information from unauthorized access.  
**Improper Conduct**

247-host.com may also use customer identifiable information to investigate and help prevent potentially unlawful activity or activity that threatens the network or otherwise violates the Terms of Service and Acceptable Use Policies.  
**Updates  
** 247-host.com may at any time, without notice to you and in its sole discretion, amend this statement from time to time. Please review this statement periodically. Your continued use of 247-host.com services after any such amendments signifies your acceptance thereof.  
**Customer Concerns  
** If you have questions or comments regarding this privacy policy you may contact us at cotact@247-host.com.   

  | 

|   

 **Key Features of Our Services**  
  
---  
* No Hidden Charges  
* Instant Set up.  
* Money Back Guarantee.  
* 24/7 Support  
* 99.99% Uptime.  
* RvSkin Included.  
* Fantastico Included.  
* Unlimited Features.  
* Daily Back up.  
* No set up Fee.  
* Low Costs  
* Multiple Payment Methods
